Jhal Jhal Jhal Hello Hello
Friends, welcome to your
own So Stop channel in Hindi, how can
you, if you have not yet subscribed to our channel, then do it
and also
I have given my Begum Tendering
in the description box, you
can go there and join the Amazon channel because I
update One Delhi News and I
share the screenshot of every share that I like,
tell me today I banked on a lot of stocks
and I have
combined a lot of them, in which after editing I have made a good
profit,
I had shared the screenshot of it on my Begum Chehra,
friends, today we will start the program
with a bang, today I have brought such a topic for you
that your soul will be satisfied,
your soul, what is that share,
friends, earning money in the share market is
not difficult but it is not easy either, it is not that it is
very difficult but it is
not that easy either because most of the people
buy good shares but buy them at an expensive rate
and then after that they invest themselves there
and start saying that I got
trapped by buying them at a higher rate, I bought this damn
share this late, now this share is going to increase
I bought Bank of India
shares at 4,000 and today they're trading
at 28,34,222,2064. It's not going up at all.
People get
so upset by the price increase. I bought
that Pooja stock at 272 for 28, and
it's stuck. Now they start crying,
tears start coming, wondering what should I do? What should I do?
What should I do? Today, we'll
see Whirlpool shares getting stuck
at 2,500. Buying good shares at good
prices is incredibly important. When the
market starts to run too fast,
our beloved retail
investor becomes the scapegoat,
and the operator traps them. The
operator first makes the market so fast that it
feels like the opportunity is gone.
When we buy a good stock too high, the
operator suddenly
crashes the market and the stock,
preventing it from rising for a long time. It falls
so low that it's hard to believe why the market is failing.  He does
n't even mention the name of the stock, it
hangs on the same dew for many months
and when retail investors exit from there, then the price
increases.
This is what often happens, we and our dear
innocent retail investors get trapped
in their trap. If we want to
invest in the stock market and become a successful investor, then
we should keep only one thing in mind.
What should we keep in mind, so keep the eyes of the serial Nighaayein. The title
of my video, the
title of my channel,
Nighaayein has been chosen very thoughtfully
because in the market you have to survive,
success is double. You make mistakes by finding your mistake,
he sees his prey
from a distance and keeps an eye on it.
When he feels that now the opportunity has come, he
seizes it. Similarly, what we have to do is
keep our eyes on it. There are a lot of shares on the stock market,
you have to keep your eyes on each one
and when we feel that a
good share is found at a good grade, then
grab it, loot it, do
not miss that opportunity.  They will let the check go, just
like the opportunity had come in a side
industry, it was such a good son,
friends, its share had fallen to 156,
such a good opportunity had come that if those
who did not want to buy at that rate, they would have got
free from their hands, today see I have done a
lot of trading in Exide Industries,
I
told all my subscribers on Amazon Video, who have joined our TV channel, to buy Nifty,
so we also bought Raja Battery, the bank
compound had
come to quit, on this date, you should invest
your heart on the stock, then you come to
1662, hey, keep quiet there for a long
time, the rest you can buy from there at 70-80, which can cause of the
opportunity to fall again,
and as soon as we got the opportunity, we grabbed it and got a good
profit,
today I have brought such an opportunity for you, I have
brought this topic with you, when you
feel that there is an opportunity in it, then you can quickly
make a small case in it,
you can take all the positions together in one hand,
what you should do is a small type
Injustice is unfair to all sectors and you
can invest a small amount here right now. You
will see that I have brought this stock in this topic.
Whenever the market is up a little bit, keep
adding to it. That is, if you
think that you can take the top of the face.
Whenever you see a drop of 35 points,
add a drop of 535 points here. And to
maintain this stock long term, this mask which I am
telling you, you will make it long-term. It is
very professional,
I would say, for swing trading,
you will make food in the long term for a month or two. If there are
shares together, then
one share will fall, some will
fall, some will run, but one will remain maintained.
And see, this will give you a lot of profit in the long term. Right now
it is a little expensive,
I think it is a little expensive right now, but if there is a
slight correction here, then
you can add, it is your choice. You
can also add speed here, but I
think the trust has become expensive, that's all that is happening right now.
I have whispered in your ears
that you should take the opportunity as soon as you see it. I
am not YouTube to tell you that this is
your choice. If you feel like
taking a laptop right now, you should take the
time and
save it by taking a three-four percent drop off box.
Now, whenever you feel that there is a three-four
percent drop here, you
can enter one here. If you feel that
we can take it on this letter also, then take it and then
when there is a five percent drop and add the
amount again on every 5 buttons,
add it on every partner drop, then it will become such a
happy investment and you can invest in it for the long term. You
can see your security profit of Rs. 2510. If you
want to edit it, you can do it.
I have given the link of this mask
in my description box. In the
description box of YouTube, I have
given the link of this original. If you want, you can use all these shares by
clicking there.
Let us discuss this with
all the seekers. Share this
with whom?  Let me tell you, all these
shares are of well known companies of insurance sector, there is
one above Adams, I have brought a
screenshot of it in small,
now we will see which are these shares,
like life insurance is SBI Life
Insurance and Butt General Insurance
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
Max Financial Services General
Insurance in the General Insurance
Corporation Indian and New India
Insurance Corporation India INSAF
I have made a small map of
just two shares, one share, one share, two shares,
one share of like and share and if
you see the total investment value of 10 shares, then the
minimum amount of one year is 10 thousand 600 64 up 2065, you will see
its return is 30%
in one year, that is, the average of all these like shares has gone
up a lot and some shares have fallen, you will
see that a good profit of 30% is being seen, if
you also do it then
you will see that you will get five percent nutrition, there is
no benefit in putting a small amount
in this market that you can invest in one segment  The
first ingredient is quite good, while
Nifty has given a return of 47.38, Nifty has
given good returns in its companies but I
feel that in the coming time it will
leave Nifty behind and this return is
ours, this good money
return of the share, now look at the current price
of all these shares, you will see that the
current price of SBI Life is 1243 today, let us
talk about the
current price of HDFC Life in September, the current price of 758,
your price to extend it is 1628 up and the
current price of the share is 60 76 above, if I
talk about GIC Army General Insurance Corporation, then
its price is 150 rupees, the
current price of NIACL is 158, the
current price of Max Furniture is
101 60, which seems good to me,
that is JIA Asian and this is a
good effort of NIACL, tight individual of Indore city should
also construct in their demat
account, I think SBI
Life has become expensive, SBI Apps Life has become
expensive today  The sale number for the
Rishi Purusha Mriga has become expensive. The rest of the match
- I think it's okay, so you should wait a little bit.
If you can call them a quick heads-up, whether it's internal or
individual, then
set the rest of the justice for all four cities.
When SBI Life reaches 1150 at one time, then you
can ban it. If this good Life
reaches around 70, then you can bike like this.
If it is around 1500 to 15 to 20, then you
can click here and
the potential is 634 to 644, then
ban it here. Set the top box so that you can
save this mall here. While it seems
that what you have set and
is of those areas, during this mall you
saw a decline of four to five questions, so if you
want, you can add it there. This
is a small slowdown of mine, the rest is your choice whether
you want to invest here or not.
I think that this is better than
seeing good returns in this.  You
can get it because it is clear that Siyaram is
investing together, so some
hair cutting will increase with some. These were the best shares with me today.
How did you like the video and our channel
Shayari? If you liked it, then do
not forget to subscribe to our channel. Please subscribe to
my YouTube channel and do forward
and share our channel and do
not forget to join our channel. The
benefit you can get from launching a TV channel is that whatever is the
latest from the share market, I keep
updating it daily from 6 to 9 in the morning and whatever I set
or edit, I keep
sharing its screenshot on my team channel. Whether you
like and share it now or
not, when I buy it, I share it within 1 to 5
minutes. These were the best
shares with me today. Please subscribe to my
YouTube channel. Thank you.